Nsababera Yvette Umurerwa

P.O. BOX 22888-00400 NAIROBI, KENYA EMAIL: umubera@gmail.com CELL: (+254) 704 577 585

Business and marketing manager, with accomplishments in content marketing and business development. Experienced in leadership and management through roles as an online marketer and overall business manager. Possesses knowledge in online marketing strategies, and ability to improve and grow a business by maximising efficiency and profitability. Works with a strong sense of responsibility, organization and creativity, with ethical conduct.

Fluent in:

•Kiswahili •French •Kinyarwanda.

Core competencies include:

•Client relations • Online marketing •Content Management •Accounting •Project Management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Intraline Online (Kenya, Uganda) 2015 - Present

Operations Manager and Business Development Manager

Spearhead the sales and marketing teams and manage logistics and order management. Implement successful growth strategies. Head of the staff recruitment process.

- Created an online order and delivery system, that attracts both online clients and offline clients that has increased revenue by 60% in the past 6 months.
- Increased productivity by 20% while simultaneously reducing headcount by 10%.

Mzoori.com (Kenya) 2015

Content Marketer

In charge of social media content and marketing. Additionally, responsible for catalogue development.

- Boosted social media awareness of Mzoori book service through online posts.
- Learnt strategies to increase social media responsiveness.

Henga Systems (Kenya) 2014 - 2015

Social Media Marketer

In charge of social media content and mobile application marketing. Additionally, responsible for catalogue development.

• Boosted social media awareness of Henga System mobile applications through events and interactive online posts.

INTERNSHIPS

AFREPREN/FWD (Kenya) March 2014 - June 2014 CORAR AG. LTD (Rwanda) March 2013 - June 2013 Kianda School (Kenya) June 2010 - March 2011

Tasks and duties:

- Customer service
- Basic accounting
- IT Support

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business and Information Technology- First Class Honours **STRATHMORE UNIVERSITY 2011 - 2015**

Certificate in Basic Information Technology CHRIST THE KING 2010

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education

MOI GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL ELDORET 2006 - 2009

Kenya Certificate of Primary Education
SAVANNAH ACADEMY NAIROBI 1996 - 2005

REFEREES

Jared Otuke System Administrator and Researcher AFREPREN/FWD

+254 725 235 708

otuke.jared@gmail.com

Julia Methu Former Mentor Strathmore University +254 736 674 361 wangarimethu@gmail.com

Solange Musabyimana Country Representative Elite Tools Rwanda +250 788 305 786

solange@eliterwanda.com